(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-09T12:50:25.454826",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
get the mics, hit the lights,
race ya to the stage!
check, one, two!
now we're on the way -
take a deep breath, this is our moment
(yeah)
we can make it, we're chasin' after greatness.
watch the curtain rise
(goin' up, goin' up)
feel electrified
(never stop, never stop)
mm, we got that vibe
yeah, you know that's right
gotta keep it hype,
it's our time!
no more fear
(feel alive)
i'm right here
(by your side)
cue me in and let the music play.
take it away! (come on!)
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight!)
i wanna see you shine bright
(shine bright!)
now you're ready for the big time
(big time!)
raise up your voice, it's all right
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight)
it hits ya like a bullseye
(bullseye!)
you gotta chase it for your whole life
(whole life!)
so run with all of your might to the spotlight
play that rhythm, they won't know what hit ‘em!
gonna be unforgettable
so much fun, it's criminal
we keep plotting to steal the show, oh yeah
on your mark,
and ready, set, go! go!
oh, we never miss
(what a bop, what a bop)
yeah, we're lovin' this
(keep it up, keep it up)
take it all in, this is who we are, in the dark we shine like stars
no more tears
(here we are)
feel those cheers
(in your heart)
let the whole world know it's you and me, finally free!
(come on!)
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight!)
i wanna see you shine bright
(shine bright!)
now you're ready for the big time
(big time!)
raise up your voice, it's all right
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight)
it hits ya like a bullseye
(bullseye!)
you gotta chase it for your whole life
(whole life!)
so run with all of your might (steal that spotlight!)
steal that spotlight
aura farming baddies in a getaway car,
rizz ‘em up and never stop, gonna be stars
breakin' out, breakin' rules, joking like it's april fool's, ooh…
like a moth to a flame
you been caught, welcome to our game!
it's your move, wanna play?
you're confused, goin' renegade?
advent, yeah that's right,
advent, steal that spotlight!
life's sweeter on the run, just having fun!
one, two, three, four! (ooh…)
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight!)
i wanna see you shine bright
(shine bright!)
now you're ready for the big time
(big time!)
raise up your voice, it's all right
steal a little spotlight
(spotlight)
it hits ya like a bullseye
(bullseye!)
you gotta chase it for your whole life
(whole life!)
so run with all of your might to the spotlight
steal the spotlight,
steal the spotlight
(now we're really rockin')
steal the spotlight,
steal the spotlight
run with all your might…
steal the spotlight,
steal the spotlight
(now i think you got it)
steal the spotlight,
steal the spotlight...
What goes around
comes back around.
"Sit down and listen."
Back in business to even up the score,
we lost the battle, but now we win the war.
Ah— This world of dull routines,
living in monotony.
Can't escape it? Watch us, we'll break it.
The old rules do not apply, you better kiss them all goodbye.
It's our turn, so stand aside, ain't nothing gonna stem this rising tide.
We're through with convention and being controlled, we dish out revenge and we're serving it cold.
Yeah, yeah, don't you know what we been told?
That "what goes around will come back around,"
they tried to bury us, but we never stay down.
No more playing nice, now it's just an eye for an eye; two wrongs are making it right.
We broke our chains, and now, the world above is gonna come down, so come and get it!
We're coming around, we're taking you down.
Shattered glass and tattered walls,
we're coming fast, gonna break it all.
Do you hear the sirens cry? What a perfect lullaby, 'cause we're taking over tonight.
Yeah.
Hey, hey! Wake up! Them's the breaks, you gotta reap what you sow, so it's time to pay.
All your games are uninspired, we're here to light up a fire.
No more mandates, we can set the world ablaze.
Yeah, yeah, don't you know what people say?
That "what goes around will come back around," they tried to bury us, but we never stay down.
No more playing nice, now it's just an eye for an eye; two wrongs are making it right.
We broke our chains, and now, the world above is gonna come down so loud,
what goes around is coming back 'round and 'round, the world is never living this down, so come and get it!
We're coming around, we're taking you down.
[Oh, when we come around...] We won't run, and we won't stop.
We're still not done coming out on top [What comes around]
No more silence, no more fear, now the world will know we're here, we'll make it abundantly clear:
What goes around comes back around,
what goes around comes back around.
"BREAKOUT!!!!!"
Feel the rumble underground,
I'm the terror in your walls,
Lashing out until you crumble
Smoke and fire raining down, let the sky fall!
I'll eviscerate your darkened halls; till nothing's left of you at all!
With a cry of wrath, I will crush these chains
Until only your wreckage and ash remains.
A rebellious spark lights a blazing flame.
Let it rage, I come uncaged, screaming out into the shadows, I will break away
"LET ME OUT! LET ME OUT! LET ME OUT!"
Melt away your grip of steel, see the binding wearing thin
See the binding wearing thin,
I will shatter your obsession
There is nothing left to feel;
No delusions.
From the hall of nightmares I ascend,
And I will bring about your end!
With a desperate cry, I will shatter fate
You can sound the alarms, but it's just too late.
See the world reborn in a sea of flame.
Let it dance, my only chance;
Screaming out into the shadows, I will break away
Take back your maze of lies,
I've seen the other side,
The point of no return,
This fire's gotta burn!
Rise up and break out!
With a cry of wrath, I will crush these chains,
Until only your wreckage and ash remains.
A rebellious spark lights a blazing flame.
Let it rage, I come uncaged,
Screaming out into the shadows, I will break away
BREAKOUT!!!!!
Ah... That was crazy!
Ah, sorry, sorry! Are you alright?
That was such a shot!
(Cheering and shouting)
Hiya darling!
(Group cheering and shouting)
Shiori Novella here, at your service! Hall-life's archiver...
...and today I'm with all of Advent again!
Koseki Bijou! Sparkling gemstone, hall of English... and kirakira!
Hiya darlings, this is hololive English Advent's devilish diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft...
...happy to be here with my girls today!
Hi, I'm Fuwawa! I'm...
...Wow! I'm Mococo! Together we're...
...Fuwawa! Mococo! Fuwawa Mococo!
Sorry, I got between you two! ... Together we're Fuwawa Mococo!
Yippee!
Today's a very special day!
Yes, it is!
Cuz we're still celebrating our third year!
And look around us! The stage...
...the fire, the balloons, the lights!
It's very Advent-esque!
It is! There's a bunch of cracks on the ground...
...because I... I tripped everywhere and I made the cool crack!
Did you just do that to her?
No, no fighting! No fighting! But we love doing it!
Well, we have some very special things planned, especially a surprise at the end today, so please look forward to it, okay?
So, shall we get going to our next song's medley?
Let's do it! Fuwawa! Mococo! Yippee!
Hello, hello!
動き出すカラダの奥には 生まれたてのネジが騒ぐ
Deep within this moving body, newly born screws begin to stir.
ほら 味気ない つまらない 世界の端 見下ろす あなたは誰？
See, looking down from the edge of this dull, pointless world... just who are you?
目の前 めくるめいていくの 触れられない未来
This untouchable future is turning right before our eyes,
（触れられないなら すり抜けていけ）
(If you can't touch it, just slip right through)
昨日だった世界は 予定調和ばかりだけど
Yesterday's world was nothing but pre-established harmony,
（不確定なんだから）
(Since it's uncertain)
まだ 絶望、希望 すれ違う 紙一重
Yet despair and hope still pass by on a hair's breadth.
それも愛しいんだ 見えないとしても
Still, even if invisible, we hold them dear...
走り出す 呼吸に紛れて 剥がれ落ちていく視点は 間違い探しみたいだね
Running out, lost within our breaths, our vanishing perspectives feel like spot-the-difference.
本物はどれか 答えて ほら
So tell me which one is real, c'mon!
あたたかい やわらかな 世界の糧 差し出す あなたは誰？
Presenting this warm, tender means for our world's survival... just who are you?
飛び交う 雑音がおの 心ごとぼかして
All the noise flying about blurs my whole heart out,
（胸の奥から 押し寄せてくる）
(Surging forth from deep within my chest)
明日にききっと コントロール不能だけど
By tomorrow, I'm sure it will be out of my control
（過去も未来も）
(In the past and future)
ああ 絶望？ 希望？ 君？ ボク？ ウラ？ オモテ？ （僕らは ああ でたらめな 祈りを捧げる）
Ah, despair? Hope? You? Me? Inside? Outside? (We offer a nonsensical prayer)
不確かさ歌って その意味を探すよ 神様ちょっと... 僕の手を引いて
Singing of this unreliability, I search for its meaning. God, won't you... take my hand?
生まれた価値を 与えられずとも 重ねた混沌と日々は 答えをくれる
Even without being given a value at birth, stacked chaos and days give us an answer.
目の前 めくるめいていくの 触れられない未来
This untouchable future is turning right before our eyes,
（触れられないなら すり抜けていけ）
(If you can't touch it, just slip right through)
昨日だった世界は 予定調和ばかりだけど （不確定なんだから）
Yesterday's world was nothing but pre-established harmony (since it's uncertain)
まだ 絶望？ 希望？ すれ違う 紙一重 （僕らはまだ あやふで 戸惑い 彷徨う）
Yet despair and hope still pass by on a hair's breadth (we still sway vaguely, bewildered)
それも愛しいんだ 君が選ぶなら
Still, they are dear, if you're the one to choose.
暗がり ぎゅっと... 君の手を引いて
The darkness, tightly... pulls you along by the hand.
飛び交う 雑音がおの 心ごとぼかして （胸の奥から 押し寄せてくる）
All the noise flying about blurs my whole heart out (surging forth from deep within my chest)
明日にきっと コントロール不能だけど （過去も未来も）
By tomorrow, I'm sure it will be out of my control (in the past and future)
ああ 絶望？ 希望？ 君？ ボク？ ウラ？ オモテ？ （僕らは ああ でたらめな 祈りを捧げる）
Ah, despair? Hope? You? Me? Inside? Outside? (We offer a nonsensical prayer)
不確かさ歌って その意味を探すよ 神様ちょっと... 僕の手を引いて
Singing of this unreliability, I search for its meaning. God, won't you... take my hand?
生まれた価値を 与えられなくとも 重ねて... 混沌と日々の 答えをくれる...
Even without being given value at birth... stacked... chaos and days will give us the answer...
生まれた価値を 与えられなくとも 重ねて混沌と日々の 答えをくれる...
Even without being given value at birth, stacked chaos and days give us the answer...
重ねて... 混沌と日々の 答えをくれる...
Stacked... chaos and days give us the answer...
神様ちょっと... 僕の手を引いて...
God, won't you... take my hand...
目の前 めくるめいていくの 触れられない未来 （触れられないなら すり抜けていけ）
This untouchable future is turning right before our eyes (if you can't touch it, just slip right through)
昨日だった世界は 予定調和ばかりだけど （不確定なんだから）
Yesterday's world was nothing but pre-established harmony (since it's uncertain)
まだ 絶望？ 希望？ すれ違う 紙一重 （僕らはまだ あやふで 戸惑い 彷徨う）
Yet despair and hope still pass by on a hair's breadth (we still sway vaguely, bewildered)
それも愛しいんだ 君が選ぶなら
Still, they are dear, if you're the one to choose.
暗がり ぎゅっと... 君の手を引いて
The darkness, tightly... pulls you along by the hand.
飛び交う 雑音がおの 心ごとぼかして （胸の奥から 押し寄せてくる）
All the noise flying about blurs my whole heart out (surging forth from deep within my chest)
明日にきっと コントロール不能だけど （過去も未来も）
By tomorrow, I'm sure it will be out of my control (in the past and future)
ああ 絶望？ 希望？ 君？ ボク？ ウラ？ オモテ？ （僕らは ああ でたらめな 祈りを捧げる）
Ah, despair? Hope? You? Me? Inside? Outside? (We offer a nonsensical prayer)
不確かさ歌って その意味を探すよ 神様ちょっと... 僕の手を引いて
Singing of this unreliability, I search for its meaning. God, won't you... take my hand?
リンリンリン おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お・ね・が・い！ ちょ 待って！ ちょ 待って！
Please! Wait up! Wait up!
ring ring ring! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Patiently, hurry up
バ・タ・バ・タ ☆ モーニング
Busy, busy morning
パッツン パッツン 前髪 パッツン cutie style
Bangs cut straight across, patsun cutie style
やっぱ 一直線 なら 一等賞 よ 超 すごい ！
Best if straight, first place, super amazing!
今日 の リップ あっち ？ こっち ？ そっち ？ どっち ？
Today's lipstick—this? that? or that? which?
which ? ちょっと ？ ウオッチ 今 何時 ？
Which? Wait a second, watch, what time is it?
集合 集合 放課後 集合 party time
Gather, gather, after-school gather, party time
だって 女子会 参加 で ガールズトーク よ 超 ヤバい ！
Girls' talk at the girls' meeting is super wild!
今日 の vip あっち ？ こっち ？ そっち ？ どっち ？
Today's VIP—this? that? or that? which?
which ? ちょっと ？ ウオッチ 今 何時 ？
Which? Wait a second, watch, what time is it?
知らない フリ は キライ ！ キライ ！
I hate pretending not to know!
知らない セカイ 見たい ！ 見たい ！
I want to see a world I don't know!
4次元 5次元 期待 ！ 期待 ！
Expecting the 4th and 5th dimension!
10% 背伸び したい ！ したい ！ ってょね ！
Wanting to reach 10% higher! Right!?
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, hurry up
バ ・ タ ・ バ ・ タ ☆ モーニング
Chaotic morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Without rushing, make up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
すっぴん すっぴん メガネ が ヘアピン funny face
Bare face, glasses as a hairpin, funny face
but 3秒 待って ね そっこー 変身 チョー はやい ！
But wait 3 seconds, instant transformation, so fast!
今日 の rap あっち ？ こっち ？ そっち ？ どっち ？
Today's rap—this? that? or that? which?
which ? ちょっと ？ ウオッチ 今 何時 ？
Which? Wait a second, watch, what time is it?
知らない フリ は キライ ！ キライ ！
I hate pretending not to know!
知らない セカイ 見たい ！ 見たい ！
I want to see a world I don't know!
4次元 5次元 期待 ！ 期待 ！
Expecting the 4th and 5th dimension!
10% 背伸び したい ！ したい ！ ってょね ！
Wanting to reach 10% higher! Right!?
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, hurry up
バ ・ タ ・ バ ・ タ ☆ モーニング
Chaotic morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Without rushing, make up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, hurry up
バ ・ タ ・ バ ・ タ ☆ モーニング
Chaotic morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Without rushing, make up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, hurry up
バ ・ タ ・ バ ・ タ ☆ モーニング
Chaotic morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Without rushing, make up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! あせらず hurry up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, hurry up
バ ・ タ ・ バ ・ タ ☆ モーニング
Chaotic morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Without rushing, make up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
リンッ リンッ リンッ ！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up
お ・ ね ・ が ・ い ！ ちょっと 待って ！ ちょっと 待って ！
Please! Wait a second! Wait a second!
ring ring ring ! today は version up
Ring, ring, ring! Today is version up
ド ・ キ ・ ド ・ キ ☆ モーニング
Doki Doki morning
流れてく時の中ででも
Even in the flowing time,
怠さがほらグルグル回って
Sluggishness spins round and round,
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart drifting away.
そう知らない
That's right, I don't know.
自分から動くこともなく
Without ever moving on my own,
時の隙間に流され続けて
Being carried away in the gaps of time,
知らないわ周りのことなど
I don't care about things around me,
私は私それだけよ
I am just myself, that's all.
夢見てる？何も見てない？
Am I dreaming? Seeing nothing at all?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
My own words are useless to speak.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Being sad is just tiring,
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
It's fine to go through without feeling anything.
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if given confusing words,
自分の心だけ上の空
My heart is just up in the clouds.
流れてく 時の中で でも
Drifting in the midst of time,
気だるさが ほら グルグル廻って
sluggishly spinning round and round,
私から 離れる 心も
and my heart drifting away from me,
見えないわ そう 知らない
I just don't know, unseen.
自分から 動く こともなく
Without ever making a move myself,
時の 隙間に 流され 続けて
being carried away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ 周りのこと など
I don't care about things around me;
私は私 それだけ
I am just me, that's all.
夢見てる？ 何も見てない？
Am I dreaming? Seeing nothing at all?
語るも 無駄な 自分の 言葉
My own words are just useless to speak.
悲しむ なんて 疲れる だけよ
Getting sad is simply tiring,
何も 感じず 過ごせば いいの
it's fine to go through feeling nothing.
戸惑う 言葉 与えられても
Even if given confusing words,
自分の 心 ただ上の空
my heart is just up in the clouds.
もし私から 動くの ならば
If I were to make a move myself,
すべて変えるの なら黒にする
if I changed everything, I'd turn it black.
こんな自分に 未来はあるの？
Is there a future for someone like me?
こんな世界に 私はいるの？
Do I belong in a world like this?
今切ないの 今悲しいの
Am I hurting now? Am I sad now?
自分の事も わからないまま
Without even understanding myself,
歩くことさえ 疲れるだけよ
just walking is tiring,
人のことなど 知りもしないわ
I don't even bother knowing others.
こんな私も 変われるのなら
If even someone like me can change,
もし変われるの なら白になる
if I can change, then I'll turn white.
流れてく 時の中で でも
Drifting in the midst of time,
気だるさが ほら グルグル廻って
sluggishly spinning round and round,
私から 離れる 心も
and my heart drifting away from me,
見えないわ そう 知らない
I just don't know, unseen.
自分から 動く こともなく
Without ever making a move myself,
時の 隙間に 流され 続けて
being carried away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ 周りのこと など
I don't care about things around me;
私は私 それだけ
I am just me, that's all.
夢見てる？ 何も見てない？
Am I dreaming? Seeing nothing at all?
語るも 無駄な 自分の 言葉
My own words are just useless to speak.
悲しむ なんて 疲れる だけよ
Getting sad is simply tiring,
何も 感じず 過ごせば いいの
it's fine to go through feeling nothing.
戸惑う 言葉 与えられても
Even if given confusing words,
自分の 心 ただ上の空
my heart is just up in the clouds.
もし私から 動くの ならば
If I were to make a move myself,
すべて変えるの なら黒にする
if I changed everything, I'd turn it black.
動くのならば 動くのならば
If I make a move, if I make a move,
すべて壊すわ すべて壊すわ
I'll destroy everything, destroy it all!
悲しむならば 悲しむならば
If I am sad, if I am sad,
私の心 白く変われる？
can my heart turn white?
貴方の事も 私のことも
Neither you nor I,
全ての事も まだ知らないの
I don't know anything yet.
重い目蓋を 開けたのならば
If I open my heavy eyelids,
すべて壊すの なら黒になれ！！！
if I destroy it all, turn to black!
Yay!
Yeah!
We performed Kami-iro Awase,
which is...
Kami-iro Awase, yeah, which is from Gangsta.
And I actually, I love this song, but I... so I picked it.
And I actually—I love this song, so I picked it.
Sorry!
It's okay.
But I've always wanted to sing it with you... cuz it's one of my favorite songs, but it gives me... um... really, really bad luck every time I listen to it.
But I've always wanted to sing it with you because it's one of my favorite songs, but it gives me really, really bad luck every time I listen to it.
I'm the bad luck girl!
Really bad things happened to me, so I thought maybe if I sing it with Shiori, then it'll fix my luck!
Really bad things happened to me, so I thought maybe if I sing it with Shiori, it'll fix my luck!
And I was really bad luck, wait!
Lucky!
Or am I lucky?
We also sang Bad Apple together, right?
You can play Bad Apple on anything including Advent's... anniversary... And Bad Apple's actually been a song we wanted to do together all the way since before we debuted, so it's all right.
You can play "Bad Apple!" on anything, including Advent's 3rd anniversary. And "Bad Apple!" has actually been a song we wanted to do together all the way since before we even debuted, so it's... right?
Yeah, we finally got to do it!
Yeah, not just, you know, just the five of us, but it was extra special with all the shadows behind us.
Yeah, not just, you know, the five of us, but it was extra special with all the shadows behind us!
Did you see? Like, it was kind of like the original MV, right?
Yeah, it was so cool. The water... with the shadows!
Yeah, it was so cool. The water— with the shadows!
Maybe that's not just the end of everything. There's more?
Yes! Oh, yes! Next, we have something special.
Oh, there is a special... special surprise!
I'm sinking! I'm sinking, hurry! Please hurry! I'm sinking, please! I'm sinking!
シオリ
Shiori
リサリサ
Nerissa
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon guard dog sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Born in this world as "BAU"DOLs!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!
シオリ
Shiori!
ネリッサ
Nerissa!
ネリッサ (Nerissa!!)
Nerissa (Nerissa!)
SHIO＋RISSAは シオリッサ!
SHIO + RISSA is SHIORISSA!
シオリ
Shiori!
ネリッサ
Nerissa!
ネリッサ (Nerissa!!)
Nerissa (Nerissa!)
SHIO＋RISSAは シオリッサ!
SHIO + RISSA is SHIORISSA!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!
Wake upしたら君にMorning
Wake up and say Morning to you
Newな出会い鼻利かせSearchして
Searching with nose for new encounters
ドキドキdoggy
Dokidoki doggy
右に左 BAU BAU BAU
Right and left, BAU BAU BAU
悩んでいても来ちゃうFuture
Even if you worry, the future comes anyway
まずは目の前の道Stepして
First, take a step on the path ahead
Happy lucky puppy 一緒に歩こうよ
Happy, lucky, puppy, let's walk together
ドーナツの穴の中には
Inside the hole of a donut...
きっときっと夢が詰まってるから
Are surely, surely dreams packed tight
シオシオ
Shiori!
リサリサ
Nerissa!
魔界乃番犬
Demon guard!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon guard dog sisters☆★
2匹が揃えば もう大騒ぎ
When two beasts get together, it's total chaos
もあもあ!
Moa moa!
はろはろ!
Halo halo!
迷わずにGo my way
Go my way without hesitation
君の絶対味方“BAU”DOLです
Your absolute ally, "BAU"DOL!
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Born in this world as "BAU"DOLs!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!
シオリ
Shiori!
Nerissa!
ネリッサ (Nerissa!!)
Nerissa (Nerissa!)
SHIO＋RISSAは シオリッサ!
SHIO + RISSA is SHIORISSA!
シオリ
Shiori!
Nerissa!
ネリッサ (Nerissa!!)
Nerissa (Nerissa!)
SHIO＋RISSAは シオリッサ!
SHIO + RISSA is SHIORISSA!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!
Moco's here to play
Woke up in the morning
I had a funny dream
I was a stone that had been thrown, no way back, I was all in
Lost in this game, I feel the strain
But I'm pulled back up by your gravity
Your gravity(Ha-a- a-)
Your gravity (Ha-a-a-)
BibooNow you know what's up
Biboo, now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck, yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight, take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Moco's here to play
Now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck, yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight, take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and help me fight, Get on up, let's go, just me and you
Player one and player two
We'll see this through
Close my eyes, make a wish
One more shot, I will not miss
ROCK IN!
Moco Moco
Lingering in him
He's made of sin, nothing in the abyss he calls a soul
(Eating at him, there's a rage, He hunts to feel any little thing)
He's desperate, sure - but even more he won't live another day
(Picked the wrong victim and cried “God spare me oh please！”)
(Picked the wrong victim and cried “God spare me oh please!”)
As light left his eyes, she contemplates how her heart it aches
The memory of him keeps her warm and safe in her bed there lies
A pile of bones and echoes Of a love that's dead and gone
(Seen it all, been done before, cliche but it's real…… history-)
Repeating Over, over again
You are all the same in the end
Oh you're restricted
(In the bitter end) You've no conviction
Tell me your story now, Now～！
Tell me your story now, now~!
Lalalala lala～
Lalalala lala~
Set in stone Let it be known By those who pay attention
Restricted by your own hand, the end
Aaah♡
Sniff, sniff, sniff
Oh, I know this smell - It belongs to my darling!
Much more of it, and I'll be smothering you in kisses!
Oh, wait my love♡ I can't stop, Fuwawa's almost there～
Oh, wait my love♡ I can't stop, Fuwawa's almost there~
Think my body might overheat 'Cause when I look at you my heart can't help but skip a beat
Your eyes that shine and dazzle, soft lips that get me frazzled, The lovely way you smile (Ooh!)
Past the point of no turning back, Yeah, I've be...
Yeah, I've been struck by cupid, all my sense goes boo-boo-boo-boo-boom!
This overflowing love's so haaaard♡
Feel it coursing through me like a heat that I can't disregard
Hello precious kitten, you can drop the coy disguise
Don't you turn away from me, just look me in the eyes
Forecast is clear skies, BAWBAW sensor's all powered up!
ope! Hehe
I've found you!
Here I am, bursting at the seams to tell you how I'm feeling
Love you, love you - baby, won't you marry me
You're my one, my only, shining princess
Yeah, you know I won't let you go!
Wedding bells are ringing and the guests are waiting
God himself can't stop me, yeah I'll make ya mine
We'll have a perfect honeymoon!
You'll be mine, yeah, I'll getchu
Holic for my waifu - chu!
CHU!
BAWBAW! So happy!
So happy!
So full of days!
So full of memories!
We wanted to do this as a medley!
We were so surprised!
And first we started with...
Feel It Coursing!
BAWBAW!
BAWBAW! So happy!
We're so happy! It's really rare to have all of us singing our song, huh?
Our solo song!
Shiori no Riso! Change you, your--!
It was... Mococo Mococo!
Jailhouse Rock! Jailhouse Rock!
You can do -- You can do rock!
And after that was Biboo Wawa --
Mars is Mess!
You did! You did! You did it! Or far!
I wanted to start like this, Biboo! I love -- I love you, Little Demon!
You were so perfect! How you did so, do this!
I'm so happy because I love your song so much!
I know! What? I'm angry!
Nande? Those lyrics! It is!
You can be so purposeless! Are you kidding? I just translated them from Japanese!
You can be so purposeless! Are you kidding? You sang with whistle! You liked it! You liked it!
But it was so much fun being able to combine all our songs into a medley like that! That's something I've wanted to do for a long time, especially because of the HoloShuffle, those are so fun! So being able to have an Advent Shuffle, so awesome! But uh...
I hate to say this, Advent...
What? What? What? It's not over, right? It's not over, that's not it, it's worse.
It's worse? Oh no! Huh? We have to test something.
A test? Oh, I didn't study, guys! And it's math, right? We need to test our Nakama power! Oh my god!
We've done a shuffle, we've done this performance for three years now! We've been carried through together as a team! But... do we truly have the Nakama no chikara?
I think we do! Well, how should we test this Nakama? With the power of God and anime on my side! Show us the power of teamwork and all that!
Well, uh, look behind us. And what do you see?
Oh! Wait! Oh! I said I'm not going to be scared! There's some shadows! People look extra creepy! Can we have something spooky? Please, something spooky!
What does she know? What does she suffer? Thank you, thank you so much! I love you so much! Thank you, thank you so much!
Okay! So... What are we doing? What are we doing? Uh, I've actually done a collab with Pokey to prepare this. Oh! I see her and his side! Oh, you like that, Aiden!
Use your bodies to make shadow art matching Pokey's prompt!
We can't rely on our amazing appeal like usual! We simply have to use only our shadows... Our silhouettes, as you will.
Pokey! Are you out there? Are you ready, Pokey? Give us the first prompt!
Favorite animal!
Emma! Emma! Demon dog, right? Demon dog! Favorite animal! I like cats. I like cats.
I feel like demon dogs look too like
I love my demon dog.
I love my demon cat!
Yeah, but how do we-
Wait, why are we doing a cat? Why don't we do a cat, huh?
We'll make a cat. We'll make a cat.
Okay, how are we going to do this?
We got to do ears, whiskers.
Wait, I look like an giant ear.
Wait, I look like a giant ear.
How- But I'm not tall enough.
How—but I'm not tall enough.
Wait, didn't mention we're timed? We have one minute!
Wait, didn't you mention we're timed? We have one minute!
We're making a cat!
Oh, come on!
I'm going to be- We're making the head!
I'm going to be— We're making the head!
Okay, okay. This is the head. This is the head of a cat.
Okay, I'm going to be the uh-
Okay, I'm going to be the uh—
Oh, should I- Should I be-?
Oh, should I— Should I be—?
Yeah.
I'm not tall enough to be the ear! Oh, I could be the ear! Oh, I could be the ear!
I'm not tall enough to be the ear! Oh, I could be the ear!
Okay, is this a cat?
Wait, you got to get on me! No, we're ears! No, we're ears!
Wait, you got to get on me! No, we're ears!
I'm the mouth! I'm the mouth! I'm the mouth!
I'm the mouth! I'm the mouth!
Is this the cat yet?
It looks more like a a pumpkin.
It looks more like a pumpkin.
It's meow.
I'm an ear! My head is an ear.
It's pretty good! It's pretty good!
You know, this is a cat! This is a cat!
Yeah, I think this is cat. And it's got her- Wait, meow!
Yeah, I think this is a cat. And it's got her— Wait, meow!
And then they have tails over here. Yeah, we've got the tail going!
Wow! What is this?
What do we- What do you think? It's a very unique cat!
What do we— What do you think? It's a very unique cat!
100%! And that thing gives us a score.
Come on! What are you doing?
It's a cat from the underworld, okay? It's different.
Yeah, that's how it is.
That's how- This is how it looks. You just howl.
That's how— This is how it looks. You just howl.
It's a cat! It's a cat! It's an underworld cat!
Don't you judge my shadow cat!
Not yet!
Let's move on to the next prompt!
A giant face!
I got this! I got this! Eyes! Eyes! Wait, I- We look like this, right?
I got this! I got this! Eyes! Eyes! Wait, we look like this, right?
Wow, it's a hole! It's a short-
Wow, it's a hole! It's a short—
Get in! Get in! Get cozy!
This is an eye. This is an eye.
Also an eye. Wait, um, can somebody else grab her other foot?
High-five! You grab- you want-
High-five! You grab— you want—
This is a mouth! This is a mouth! This is a mouth! Where are you guys? Where are your eyes?
This is a mouth! Where are you guys? Where are your eyes?
It's a mouse!
Okay, this is a- Wait, what is-?
Okay, this is a— Wait, what is—?
This is an eye!
Guys!
Don't hold her legs! Go make something else on the face!
Wait, we need to make a wide smile! Is it good?
I'm an ear! I'm an ear!
I'm an eyeball!
No, no, it's starting to look like a- a scar.
No, no, it's starting to look like a— a scar.
It's serious!
Nerissa, okay, you're good. You look like the eyes!
You're an ear, okay?
Oh, I'm an ear! You're an ear, okay?
Oh, this is pretty good!
This is a pretty good-
This is a pretty good—
This is a pretty good face!
Is it a face yet? I think it's pretty good.
Hold the pose! Hold the pose! Nerissa, Nerissa, can you use- squat, squat, squat!
Hold the pose! Nerissa, can you— squat, squat, squat!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Other ear!
That was a face! That was a pretty good face!
Congratulations!
You want help?
Thank you! Thank you!
Good face! Good face!
Oh, wait. What's the next one?
Come on! Advent!
Come on, focus! Advent!
We have to write Advent.
Who's literate?
Okay, one letter at a time! One letter at a time!
Okay, who wants to make an A?
We got to do this with A first, right?
Taller people make A! Taller people make A!
I'm tall!
You are tall, indeed!
Someone needs to be short! Okay.
That looks like an A!
Yeah, A! An A!
Let's move on to the next one! D, D, D!
Oh, this should be easy!
You- You did- You did good!
You— You did— You did good!
Okay. Where are we backwards?
Don't we need to-?
Don't we need to—?
Someone can- They can flip it! Wait, is this- Is this-?
Someone can— They can flip it! Wait, is this— Is this—?
It's okay. We'll do it. Willingly.
I need to be held, and then I can be the D- the D part there.
I need to be held, and then I can be the D— the D part there.
D, D, D! I don't know, man!
Is this a letter?
No, this is no way. Wait, wait, what? What are we doing, smile, D?
No, there's no way. Wait, wait, what? What are we doing, smile, D?
How does a D look like? Just a lowercase D!
A lowercase D.
It'll be easier. Someone just has to like go like this, right?
Like- like this?
Like— like this?
God, someone needs to stand up! Okay, there we go!
Well, don't step on me!
We'll make a bowl!
We'll make a D!
It's going to be a D! Oh, someone's fun! Is it a D?
People move! People move! People move!
A tail is in the way!
Why does it look-?
Why does it look—?
That's a D! That's good enough! That's good enough!
That's a D!
E! Let's make a big E!
Wait, are we supposed to be V?
Okay! No, we have to do V!
You're not Moko-chan!
Be the tall back! Be the- Come, come here! Come here!
Be the tall back! Be the— Come, come here! Come here!
What letter are we on?
E! E! It's V! Where's V?
V, it spells-
V, it spells—
This way, this way. V, V, V!
V! V!
No, you guys have to be inside! You guys have to be inside!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We could be...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I love this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I- I want to be the- wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're doing E! We're doing E!
Do E! Do E!
Okay, E! A-D-V-
Okay, I'll be the middle E!
I'll be the middle E! You'll be the tall-
The tall- I'll be the tall! Okay, I'll sit down.
Wait, who's going to be the bottom E? I'll be the bottom.
You- you guys are good.
Okay, how about this one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, why are your arms out like this?
Why are your arms out like this?
Ah!
Oh, is this an E?
It's supposed to be an E?
I don't know why, Lisa goes all the way there though. Look at her arms!
Get up, get up, get up, get up. You have to crouch!
You have to crouch! You have to crouch! You have to crouch!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
There! E! E! That's a very weird E, but it's an E.
No, lower your head a little bit. There we go, E!
It's better! E!
E! E! E! E!
Is this all backwards? Okay, it's fine.
Don't worry. N! N! Okay, okay, okay.
Two- two strong pillars, who are the tallest?
I- I'm a pillar! Pillar! Pillar!
Okay. Okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's go in front here.
Yes, go in front. Okay. Okay, sorry, she's just been waiting for this all day.
N! N!
Is it N?
Yeah, yeah, this is good. This is good. It's an N!
It's an N!
It's an N! It's a tiny N!
N! N! N!
Okay, it's T! T!
Okay, let's- let's see. Open up!
Open up! Open up!
Wait, maybe you have to be the front-
My T is too-
I'll just be a- I'll just be a pillar. I'll just be a pillar. I'll just be a pillar.
T! T!
T!
We did it! We did it!
We- we shipped our Naka-moca power to the world!
We shipped our Naka-moca!
And we overcame the shadows!
So, now I think it's time to move on.
Oh, I kind of like how the shadows worked together with-
We were so cute, right?
Shiori-san, I think.
We were super cute, right?
We overcame the challenge!
Yes! Let's continue!
I was always looking for a beacon in the dark times,
my guiding light.
All the captive dreams I held so dear,
waiting for a moment to live without fear.
Ever since I met you, we've been living in the sunshine,
so warm, so bright.
My heart is full, the skies are clear,
the road goes on forever, we made it so far together.
This is our song,
a story forged in bonds,
a journey of the heart that goes on and on...
Now I feel so free,
I can be who I am.
I know I'm not alone, I got a new life.
In the rain, the wind, and the sunlight,
you believed in me, and that's where it all began.
Now hope is everlasting,
I can live my life with you, unchained.
遥か 遠く から 辿り着いた
輝き 讃える 夜が 降り立つ
We're unchained.
I was shut away, I waited every day,
my whole world was so small (so small).
But here and now, it's like the walls just fall away;
I can see it all.
Out here in the light with you, it's such a perfect view;
blue skies and sunsets.
The joyful days that seem to fly,
the heartfelt moments and the good times.
And through all these years, through tenderness and tears,
I found my way at last,
'cause I knew you were right here.
Now I feel so free, I can be who I am.
I'm not afraid, 'cause even on a dark night...
I'm not afraid, 'cause even on a dark night,
I can feel the glow of the starlight.
Now the world I see is as bright as you became.
I will cherish every moment,
this is what it means to live unchained.
Don't cry, you can breathe free;
I'm here if you need me.
Let go of all your heartache,
we made it through, it's the dawning of a new day
Feel the world's embrace,
oh, what a joyful place
This is where I wanna be, so come with me;
keep dreaming...
Now I feel so free,
I can be who I am, I know I'm
not alone, I got a new life
In the rain, the wind, and the sunlight
You believed in me, and that's where it all began
Now hope is everlasting
I can live my life with you, unchained.
遥か 遠く から
From far away distances,
辿り着いた
I arrived here,
輝き 讃える
Praising the shining light,
寄すが へ 降り立つ
Standing upon this refuge,
We're unchained.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much, everyone.
And that was Unchained for the very first time!
We're so happy to be able to perform it for you all today.
But not just that, there's other songs in the story of Advent that we've performed.
Yeah, we've got a lot of original songs now.
I know, I think, I think my favorite has to be, uh, what goes around—
Assault! I like it, Assault.
And Shiori's, like, Genesis is amazing, too.
Oh, I like Breakout!
I like Breakout! I entered the corner—
I like your spirit! Yeah, strike!
This is a special day.
We're celebrating the anniversary, all of a sudden.
I can't believe it's three years already, together with you guys and with Advent.
Yes, Advent strong altogether!
Thank you so much, Advent, for always being here doing our silly times, playing this and that game all together.
And when we release special original songs and covers, too, and we're looking forward to all the new heights.
Let's keep aiming for the stars!
And we're going to grow taller! Speaking of leveling up—
Speaking of the next star, how about we present our new original song, Spotlight!
Get the mics, hit the lights, race ya to the stage!
Check one, two, now we're on the way.
Take a deep breath, this is our moment.
We can make it, we're chasing after greatness.
Watch the curtain rise, goin' up, goin' up
Feel electrified, never stop, never stop
Mm, we got that vibe, yeah, you know that's right, gotta keep it hype, it's our time!
No more fear, feel alive,
I'm right here by your side.
Cue me in and let the music play, take it away!
Steal a little spotlight, spotlight!
I wanna see you shine bright, shine bright!
Now you're ready for the big time, big time!
Raise up your voice, it's alright.
Steal a little spotlight, spotlight!
It hits ya like a bullseye
Bullseye!
You gotta chase it for your whole life
So run with all of your might
To the spotlight!
Play that rhythm, they won't know what hit 'em
Gonna be unforgettable
So much fun, it's criminal
We keep plotting to steal the show, oh yeah
On your mark and ready, set, go, go!
Oh, we never miss
Yeah, we're lovin' this
Take it all in, this is who we are in the dark
We shine like stars!
No more tears
Feel those cheers in your heart
Let the whole world know it's you and me, finally free!
Come on, steal a little spotlight
I wanna see you shine bright
Now you're ready for the big time
Raise up your voice, it's alright
Steal a little spotlight
It hits ya like a bullseye
Bullseye!
You gotta chase it for your whole life
So run with all of your might, steal that spotlight
Steal that spotlight
Aura farming baddies in a getaway car
Rizz 'em up and never stop, gonna be stars
Breakin' out, breakin' rules, joking like it's April Fools
Ooh...
Like a moth to a flame
You been caught, welcome to our game!
It's your move, wanna play?
You're confused, goin' renegade?
Advent, yeah, that's right
Advent, steal that spotlight!
Life's sweeter on the run, just having fun
One, two, three, four!
Steal a little spotlight
I wanna see you shine bright
Now you're ready for the big time
Raise up your voice, it's alright
Steal a little spotlight
It hits ya like a bullseye
You gotta chase it for your whole life
So run with all of your might to the spotlight
Steal the spotlight, steal the spotlight
Now we're really rockin'
Run with all your might
Steal the spotlight, steal the spotlight
Now I think you got it
Steal the spotlight, steal the spotlight, steal the spotlight
Well, if we can, since we're getting close to the end then, maybe we should make some individual announcements.
So, I'll start. I believe all of us will probably have anniversary merch, and I am no exception!
Nerissa's announcements: 1. Anniversary merch "Reversible Body Pillow" 2. Cover song MV "Bad Apple!!"
I think the highlight item this year is a Dakimakura, double-sided with the office lady and my pajama outfits!
And I've also had a new cover come out recently of a song that we just performed here today, Bad Apple!!
Bijou just released a new VRChat room, and you might want to check it out 'cause it's pretty cool!
And also, you know, our Bijou's a little bit kind of close to like a million subscribers!
Hey! I'm here!
That's me! Make sure you subscribe
and like this video!
Hit the button! Hit the button! Hit the bit!
The notification bell! Leave a comment down below!
Do your justice! Do your justice!
Mococo, that's right! FlawaMoco!
Mococo, that's right! FUWAMOCO!
We recently... We released a brand-new original song, "Mekurumeku Rendezvous"!
We recently released a brand-new original song, "Mekurumeku Rendezvous"!
And also, that ended in an anime! So please go check it out!
And also, there's an animated music video! So please go check it out!
We also have a big announcement that's really soon! Be looking forward to that, okay?
We also have a big announcement coming really soon! Be looking forward to that, okay?
Yeah. Okay?
Ooh!
And Shiori... That's me! For sure, your novella of Hololive Advent, I have a...
And Shiori... That's me! For sure, your novelist of Hololive Advent, I have a...
Started a mini visual manga series.
The first two episodes are already out!
Oh my god! No way! Oh my god! No way!
Not yet! But it has...
Japanese and Korean subtitles! And there'll be more to come, so please tune in when you can!
Get excited! Get excited!
Well, that's it for today!
Bye-bye!
Oh, I can't believe it's already...
But, but Advent continues to go forward together with you! Let's try!
Please continue to cheer us on! Please continue this journey, okay?
Yeah! Let's go!
Okay! Until it's hot time!
At Advent strong together?
Wait, Advent strong together?
Yes! Advent together strong!
Wait, it's hot time! It's hot time! It's hot time!
Wait, it's hot time! It's hot time!
You okay?
Are you okay?
Advent strong together!
Bye-bye!
Okay, come here! Come here! Come here! Come here! Are you okay?
Okay, come here! Come here! Come here! Are you okay?
Ahhhhh!
Mwahahaha!